As Wise Man Christopher moved to the overflow congregation at The SCOAN,
the power of God was present to heal, to deliver, and bless them.
Prayerfully touching her in the name of Jesus Christ, the power of the Holy Ghost uncovered the darkness
locking within this woman's life, and the supernatural power of God began to crush
every demonic stronghold in her life.
Let's watch and see her deliverance.
All over your body - fire!
Now speak out - who are you?
She is my wife and you know it.
Why are trying to break a home?
Are you trying to separate me from my wife?
When I married her, you were not there.
You never made vows. Who are you to come between two married people?
How many of you are living in her?
We are five.
Mention your names.
Frustration, unemployment, death.
Who is the last person?
She is a deceiver.
Who made her to be deceiving?
Me; she is my wife.
How does she deceive?
She is a schemer. She cheats on me and covers her track.
Now, I’m dealing with her and in a matter of time, she is going to die.
Her life is in my hands and nobody, neither you or whoever, will take her away from me.
What is your position in the place you are living?
I am destroying lives.
You destroy lives?
Yes.
How do you go about destroying lives? How?
Accidents; I break homes.
How do you break homes?
I hook her up with married men.
You hook her up with married men?
Yes. All married men like her and you know it.
All married men do what?
How does she capture married men?
She has beautiful eyes.
Bedroom eyes.
What do you mean by that?
Can’t you see? Look at her; that is what I am talking about.
What is in her eyes?
Power.
What kind of power?
That attracts men.
OK, let’s talk man to man. Leave my wife alone and I will leave you alone.
How does she use the power in her eyes?
It attracts men, OK?
Use it the way you use it to attract men.
Can’t you see? Oh no, did you drug me?
When they look at her eyes - what happens to them?
You will start falling for her, hate your own wife and see her as an ugly beast.
They will hate their own wives?
Yes!
And they will come after this lady?
Yes, because she betrayed me and I have been punishing her and she doesn't get it.
That is why I take her to bars, clubs and beat her up.
She is always bruised as you can see.
I make her drunk and I beat her; I sleep with her and when the father of her baby comes,
he finds disaster and I like when they fight.
You know what? Her future is in my hands; she will never get employment.
That stupid hair salon she just opened, she will never find business.
She is always running at a loss until the 10th of July, when she’ll leave this world.
She will die on the 10th of July. Do you know that?
Why?
Last year, she escaped from me when I caused her that fatal accident.
She survived by a slim chance but this time around, I will not let her escape.
I am taking her to the dark side.
How do you want to go about that on the 10th of July?
Every year in July, I cause accidents, so that she would die and we would drink her blood
for powers for me and my friends.
You said that you capture men with the power in your eyes.
Yes.
How many of them do you normally capture in a day?
In a day, just three; it depends.
But every single day, men fall for her, no matter what.
Where do they normally take her to?
You know what - it just depends, but what I know is that they will keep following her, calling her,
leaving messages in the sent items and they will fight with their wives at the end of the day.
Answer me - how many men do you capture in a day with the power in your eyes?
It depends but mostly in the clubs.
You made her to be going to the clubs?
She goes – can’t you see? She smokes, drinks and can dance.
I did not know she was coming here. I did not know how it happened
all the way from Botswana to Nigeria.
What is in The SCOAN that you hate?
She came here to see T.B. Joshua; she thinks he is the end of her problems.
What is in Prophet T.B. Joshua that is against you?
We live in two different worlds – he lives in the light, we live in the dark.
What do you do to those married men, their marriages, to their wives?
Hurting them makes me feel much better.
They fall for her and don’t love their wives anymore.
They want divorce and marry her because she is a queen.
How many have divorced because of you?
Two or three and others are still fighting as she speaks.
Leave my wife alone, I want to go before I fight you man to man.
I have been patient with you, so now take your thing.
She thinks she is clever but I am more clever than her.
So right now your end has come.
Fire in the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Out!
In Jesus' name.
Amen.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
How are you?
I am fine, sir. How are you?
What happened to you?
Nothing.
You are delivered. Follow Jesus.
Thank You, Lord, for delivering me!
Thank You, Jesus!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Victoria. I am from Botswana.
You are very welcome. Can you first tell us what the problems were that brought you to The SCOAN?
Spiritual husband, excessive drinking and smoking.
OK. We want to go from the very beginning. How did this problem start in your life?
At what age did you begin to have these experiences?
It started when I was a young girl in grade four.
Men would visit me in my dreams and sleep with me.
That was in your dreams?
Yes.
OK. As you grew older, what did these evil spirits begin to push you to do in terms of your lifestyle.
They pushed me to do bad things such as sleeping around with married men,
having lustful relationships with them and breaking their homes.
We would go out to night clubs and they would buy me many drinks.
They would buy me clothes and give me money to sleep with them.
At the end of the day, they would go back home and I would just collect money from them
and go where I had to be.
You would meet these married men in clubs and they would then begin to buy you things.
What would happen in your relationship with them?
The only relationship I had with them was just to mingle around.
During their spare time, they would call me when they were free from their homes.
They would try to excuse themselves to come and see me.
Sometimes, I would see them as they were doing other household duties.
What would happen to these men in terms of the relationships with their wives,
once they got in contact with you, began the relationship with you.
What would happen to them with their wives?
They would fight and quarrel to the extent that their wives would start calling and insulting me
and I would do the same.
At the end of the day, the men would protect me.
The men you met would begin to love you even more than their wives?
Yes, they would start falling for me instead of their wives.
Whenever they were away from me, they would start calling me, begging for spare time.
What other things were you collecting from these married men?
What would be the things you would be taking from them?
I would be collecting money, clothes and other gifts.
Aside from the issue of going around and sleeping with married men,
what other things did this spirit push you to do in the area of men?
How would you break men's homes and hearts?
I was a heart-breaker because I would date someone my age
but when they were ready to settle down, I wouldn’t settle down with them.
I would tell them that I wouldn’t settle down for less.
Even if somebody cried out loud or went to my family for reconciliation, I would not listen to them.
I would just tell them that I had made up my mind and I had nothing to do with them,
and that's the way it is.
How did you feel each time you broke a man's heart?
Every time they cried or said it, I would just laugh.
It made me really happy that I was a diva.
I think we can understand what our sister is saying.
That evil spirit really had pushed her to do so many things,
especially in the area of relationships with men.
It pushed her to be breaking the hearts of men she went out with,
and she said that that spirit actually made her happy any time she saw these men cry
because there was a spiritual husband that was pushing her to do such things.
Sister, can you explain to us apart from these experiences and encounters with men
what other areas did these evil spirits push you into in terms of your lifestyle?
You mentioned earlier you were drinking excessively.
Can you just explain a little bit more about your lifestyle at that time?
It destroyed me to the extent that I was always disappointed and felt betrayed.
Whatever I did or wherever I went, I felt so disappointed and started hating myself
to the extent that I would not go to work.
I run my own business.
I would call my employees and tell them, "I am not feeling well, so fill my job for me and do the rest;
I will see you in the evening".
Sometimes, I did not go there and told them that my son was not well.
I would be lazy and lose a lot of money.
Tell us - would you be going out to clubs?
When you go out to clubs, what were the kinds of things you would be drinking,
and what would be happening there?
I would start drinking early at around 9 am almost every day.
I would smoke and end up going to night clubs at around midnight where I would drink whiskey,
tequila, savanna dry, up to 24 bottles a day.
I went home and would wake up with my bag and shoes on.
I would ask myself, "How did I end up home?
The last thing I remember was that I was dancing in a night club".
You would drink to the point where you would lose consciousness, and then from the night club,
you would just find yourself back in your house?
I would find myself bruised and ask my fiancé, "How did I get here?"
Sometimes, he would be sleeping and I would be out drinking with my friends.
I would ask him, "How did I get here?
Did you go and pick me up at the club?"
He said, "No, your friends came here and you passed out.
Actually, I was the one who took you out of the car to our bed".
Sometimes, he would find messages and start hitting me
but I would not fight for myself because I was under the influence of drugs.
I would not even know what was going on.
We just want to understand, how much alcohol were you taking on a daily basis?
Just give us an idea of how much.
On a daily basis, I would take 24 bottles of savanna dry, 1 bottle of jameson whiskey,
and on top of that I would take shots of tequila or springbok.
We can understand how severe our sister's alcohol addiction became as a result of this evil spirit
that was pushing her into such a lifestyle.
You mentioned that in the midst of this you were also smoking. Is that right?
Yes. Whenever I started drinking...
When I was not drinking, I would not smoke but when I drank, I would start smoking.
Even when my fiancé asked me not to smoke,
I would say that I would smoke no matter what and I became arrogant.
I would go to the ladies and start smoking.
I would get a packet of "Peter" or "CA" and then I would start smoking on my own.
My fiancé would say, "Victoria, you have been smoking"
and I would say, "Yes I've been smoking, these are my lungs".
I didn’t see any problem with it.
The following day, I would not feel well and I would feel weak but the same thing continued.
I went to work because where my shop is, there is a bar.
When I got there, I'd send them to the bar to get me alcoholic drinks.
I would drink it and after a few minutes, I would go outside and start smoking.
We just want to understand this well.
In the midst of all of these experiences, excessive drinking, smoking, going out with various men,
enjoying breaking their hearts...
Once again - what kind of dreams were you having during this period?
I would watch different "soapies" and the male characters would appear to me
at night and start sleeping with me.
My spiritual husband would visit me through the people I liked - through the models,
actors, singers and so on and so forth.
Sometimes, when I woke up, I would find myself wet. Just to be sure that you know what...
It wasn’t a dream but it was real.
I hope we understand what our sister is saying.
She said that she would watch programs on TV, especially soap operas or films,
and the spiritual husband would take the form of a character in those TV programs
and appeared to her in her dreams and sleep with her.
The following morning she would find out that she had released, that she was wet physically.
All of this was a result of this spiritual husband that was inside of you, right from a young age.
Is that right?
That is true.
We want you to tell us...
We want to understand from you Madam - how you actually find out about Emmanuel TV
and tell us about your journey to The SCOAN.
My aunties always told me about Emmanuel TV and the man of God.
I didn’t believe him (Prophet T.B. Joshua); I said, "That's magic".
One day, after a hectic night of dancing and drinking, I was lazying around in my sitting room,
laying on my couch and playing with the remote control.
I came across a Christian channel and thought that if I could get this channel,
there must be Emmanuel TV.
So, I kept scrolling until I found Emmanuel TV.
I watched and watched and I thought,
"Oh my God, this spiritual husband, what is happening to me?"
I saw people confessing and I said, "This is not me".
I was struggling to find a job and my business wasn’t doing well.
I called my friend and I asked her, "Where is this Emmanuel TV?"
She said, "In Lagos". I asked, "Where is Lagos?" She said, "In Nigeria".
That was this year, February.
That was when I went to see my auntie who once visited The SCOAN.
She helped me to fill in the papers and I came to The SCOAN last week, Wednesday.
When I came here, I was seated there and the wise men started ministering in the church.
They were going around, touching our foreheads.
When Wise Man Christopher came, he realised there was a giant inside of me
because he said, "Speak out, you demon! Who are you?"
He could see that there was a giant who was using my eyes in any form of power.
I tried to keep quiet but he started provoking it.
The demon was arrested and I went to sleep with it like that on Saturday night
but on Sunday, I was delivered here at The SCOAN.
Glory be to God Almighty!
We can actually see on the screen here, when our sister came and you can see
how that evil spirit was manifesting, saying so many things.
Tell us, sister - for the benefit of those waiting for deliverance today - what was your experience
as the Wise Man prayed for you. How did you feel in your body? Just explain more.
I had been prayed for before; I had attended so many churches back home.
When he touched me, I thought "What is he doing?"
I didn’t realise that I was going to receive fire.
When he said, "In the name of Jesus", I saw a lot of stars.
The next thing was I woke up from the floor.
I didn’t really know what happened.
Afterwards, I felt so light.
I was happy all over; I felt like I could shout to the whole world
that finally after all these years that I had been suffering, I was freed.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
To the glory of God, sister, tell us - ever since your deliverance,
what are the changes that Jesus has brought into your life.
Since my deliverance you can see me smiling; I sleep like a baby. Indeed, I'm a new-born.
I sleep like a new baby and I'm so light. I don’t have problems.
Before, I had this bad temper.
Even if I received a text message, I would get so angry that I could crush somebody or ground them.
Nowadays, even when someone calls me and talks negatively, I just take it.
One of my friends called me and said, "Oh, we saw you on TV…"
Then, I said, "God bless you. Next time, it will be you".
Now, I am free and light. I feel like a new-born.
Hallelujah! This is the evidence of deliverance, and I believe that is the same deliverance
many of us are waiting for today.
Our sister's testimony is a great inspiration to us.
Sister, you said that before coming here, you were addicted to alcohol to the point
you could take over 24 bottles of hard liquor every day.
Since your deliverance, what can you say about alcohol and any desire you have for it?
Believe me, when I get home, I will not touch alcohol.
I recently dreamt that I was at a fairground with many people and there were games.
I came across a plastic bag with two cans of beer and one bottle or water.
I picked it up, opened it and found that there were two cans of alcohol and a bottle of water inside it.
I went all around the fairground until I found the owner of the plastic bag
and then, in my dream, I gave him the beers but took out the water.
Indeed, I have been delivered.
I will never go back to drinking, smoking or cheating.
Glory be to God. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sister, early on you mentioned that when Wise Man Christopher prayed for you,
he identified that there was power in your eyes.
Could you just explain - what can you say about your eyes
and the strange power you realised you had in your eyes before the deliverance?
It started when I was in grade 7.
A certain man came to me and said, "Wow, I love your eyes".
I said, "OK, thanks."
When I started growing up, every man, everywhere I went,
would fall for my eyes, especially in the night clubs.
Whenever I was drinking at the counter, they would come and propose and start talking about my eyes.
I didn’t even know that they possessed evil power.
Every man fell for my eyes, even my fiancé.
That was how the devil really hooked me up.
What is your word of encouragement and advice to viewers around the world right now,
especially those, who are in the same problem you were once in, being addicted to alcohol, smoking,
cheating around with many boyfriends and men - what is your advice to them now that you are delivered?
I would advise them to come to Jesus.
Jesus is alive. He lives. He never said goodbye.
It is never too late to repent.
The doors of the house of the Lord are always open 24/7.
Just give your faith to the Lord and give Him all your heart, mind and strength.
In everything you do, praise Him each moment you live.
Amen. One more time, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
The evidence of Jesus is lives changed as we can see.